const questionList = [
    {
        questionNumber: "1 of 10",
        question: "What keyword is used to declare a variable in JavaScript?",
        answerChoices: ["1. var", "2. let", "3. const", "4. all of the above"],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        questionNumber: "2 of 10",
        question: "Which of the following is used to comment a single line in JavaScript?",
        answerChoices: ["1. //", "2. /**/", "3. #", "4. --"],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        questionNumber: "3 of 10",
        question: "What is the correct way to write an IF statement in JavaScript?",
        answerChoices: ["1. if (condition) {}", "2. when (condition) {}", "3. case (condition) {}", "4. choose (condition) {}"],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        questionNumber: "4 of 10",
        question: "How do you access the length of an array in JavaScript?",
        answerChoices: ["1. array.size", "2. array.count", "3. array.length", "4. array.sizeOf"],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        questionNumber: "5 of 10",
        question: "What function is used to print content to the console in JavaScript?",
        answerChoices: ["1. console.print()", "2. console.log()", "3. console.display()", "4. console.add()"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        questionNumber: "6 of 10",
        question: "What is the purpose of the === operator in JavaScript?",
        answerChoices: ["1. Assignment", "2. Equality (strict)", "3. Inequality", "4. Logical AND"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        questionNumber: "7 of 10",
        question: "Which built-in function is used to convert a string to an integer in JavaScript",
        answerChoices: ["1. toInteger()", "2. parseInt()", "3. stringToNumber()", "4. convertToInt()"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        questionNumber: "8 of 10",
        question: "What does the 'DOM' stand for in the context of web development with JavaScript?",
        answerChoices: ["1. Data Object Model", "2. Document Order Model", "3. Dynamic Object Model", "4. Document Object Model"],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        questionNumber: "9 of 10",
        question: "How do you declare a function in JavaScript?",
        answerChoices: ["1. function myFunction() {}", "2. def myFunction() {}", "3. func myFunction() {}", "4. declare function myFunction() {}"],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        questionNumber: "10 of 10",
        question: "Which event is triggered when a user clicks on an HTML element?",
        answerChoices: ["1. onHover", "2. onMouseOver", "3. onClick", "4. onKeyPress"],
        correctAnswer: 2
    }
];

